Now, speaking of money, do you owe
Amanda Seal some bread? Foley, I'm glad
you brought this up. Lord have mercy.
So, look. So, let me set it up. A year
ago, she called you out on Shannon
Sharp's show and you took the audio, put
it on the floor. Yeah. She's talking
about $2,000
from a bond that she had to pay for me,
right?
Um, should I tell the whole truth D? Go
ahead and put it out there. No, don't
put it all the way out there. I I Well,
I mean, I can put a spin on it or put it
out there. I ain't going to do that cuz
I ain't gonna throw nobody under the
bus. I gonna throw you under the bus. I
ain't gonna put it out there. I'm
all right. Look, so
I had a situation. She She um sent
sister money to come look out for me on
the situation I had. Mhm.
But this what end up happening. This is
the honest to God truth. So when the
when the um the COVID bet awards,
whatever year that was, when everybody
was quarantined and all this, you know,
like somebody had got sick on her
production team with the co I had been
quarantining with her cuz I had been
over in the crib with her, you know, we
was messing around, right? Yeah. So
I had a play I had to make. It was for
like 28,000. I had some some guys coming
in the city from where I was from. They
didn't know nobody. They knew I knew a
lot of people. I could point them in the
right direction. They came out, you
know, cuz they trust my business. You
know what I'm saying?
So, I'm trying to make this happen cuz I
needed the money.
She tell me
she needs me to help her
set all the cameras up, the microphone
wiring from downstairs, some van they
had, you know how these production teams
work. Yeah. I had to singlehandedly do
all this, right? They told me that the
payout on it was $10,000. So I looked at
her. I said, "Damn, I'm about to take a
$16,000 hit. If I don't go make this
play, they going to go bump into
somebody else and somebody else going to
make this money, right?"
But she was like my chick at the time.
Well, not Yeah. She like my chick at the
time. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Relationship.
We was trying to figure it out. All
right. Complicated cuz I'm a street
[ __ ] So that was bothering her like
cuz I had just caught a case, too. So I
was fighting back like trying to get on
my feet. But she don't know like I'm I'm
a cold [ __ ] for real. Like I mean she
can feel it. That's why she was [ __ ]
with me. But I didn't meet her on my
upscale. I met her
on my down slide.
So I'm like, damn. I'm about to take a
$16,000 hit. I'm like, it's my [ __ ]
She rich. This ain't going to be my
first play. Somebody else will call or
something will fall out the sky. [ __ ]
it. I did it.
10,000 said you don't give me 10,000 for
doing it. I'm like, [ __ ] it. Whatever.
But the thing was I thought it was a one
day job and it carried on into three
days. Oh. And me and her are not
compatible enough for us to be around
each other three days straight. Like I
got to go to Al crib, get a break for a
minute, you know? She come give me a
call me, send me a Uber, Al, send me a
car over there. Like it was [ __ ] like
that. You know what I cuz I ain't even
have a I got a B in Cali now, but I
didn't have a whip in Cali at the time.
So
three days like I say. So we bickering,
bitching back and forth.
Mhm. Third day go pass, we get into it,
I leave. Okay. You know what I'm saying?
So the way we got into it,
I really didn't even like want to
compensate with her no more. Right. Mhm.
So,
we had did something with uh Khalise and
uh Michael Rapaort. It was like some
cooking show and she gave me like she
asked me to go on a cooking show with
her. I don't know why I agreed to it,
but I did. You know what I'm saying? She
told me she' pay me to do it. So, I was
like, "Fuck it." You know what I'm
saying? She gave me like 7,000 cash
after I did it. Mhm. And it's my [ __ ]
So, I ain't care what she gave me. I
wasn't even tripping over.
So now fast forward. So I've been over
here three days. I leave. We get into
it. I don't want to kick it with her for
real cuz y'all know she obnoxious as
[ __ ] Everybody know this. The world
know this.
So I try to reach out to the people
that's supposed to pay me the 10,000.
They tell me no, it was 10,000 a day. It
wasn't 10,000.
It wasn't 10,000
for me just doing it. It was 10,000 per
day, right? Or close to it. Somewhere up
in there, right?
So, I never got any of that money. Whoa.
Because she never followed up to help me
get the cheese. And you know, I'm a
street [ __ ] I don't know who to call
for production. I don't know how to
chase a BET [ __ ] down or none of that.
So, I just chocked it. you know, it was
just better for me to just leave the
whole situation alone, right? So, what
end up happening is I guess she thought
I was
some slouch sock ass [ __ ] that wasn't
going to get back on my D and back on my
aame or something. So when she seen me I
guess like making noise about this that
this and the third or you know flashing
money or something on the internet or
some [ __ ] like that just for some
content or just cuz I'm over there with
the gas and we just ghetto as [ __ ] in
real life and this just what we do like
this some you know this a
some hood [ __ ] you feel me? She had
reached out one day and like commented
on like, "Well, you flashing all this
money, this that you can give me my
money." And I'm like, "Man, you I never
got paid for the one shit." Like, "What
is what you talking about? You talking
about $2,000. [ __ ] you rich." In fact,
like when I wasn't down, I ain't buy you
a couple Gucci bags and all type of [ __ ]
like like just people just petty as
[ __ ] bro. You know what I'm saying? It
just seemed like she just wanted
something to say. She didn't have to be
boisterous or go public about no [ __ ]
like that. Like, I ain't [ __ ] with you
in years. I don't even speak on that.
Like, don't nobody know but us for real.
Like, like I don't be popping it on
Mandy name. You know what I'm saying?
She's not the uh first uh so-called
celebrity I didn't crushed with or
crushed on. Like, I just don't run my
mouth about my business. You know what
I'm saying? But no hard feelings. You
know what I'm saying? I'm always love
the love I got for Mandy. But, you know,
sometime like you just I don't know. We
just wasn't on the same mental plane.
You know what I'm saying? Are you guys
in a good space now? I mean, we we in
the same space we was in when I left.
So, we got to be in a good space cuz I
don't have no bad blood for her. I don't
got no bad blood for nobody, Mandy. So,
I always love like if you ask me, it
sound like a crack like she wanted me to
come back home or something. That's what
it sound like. Like she missed this
[ __ ] So, you miss this little
[ __ ] baby. Is that something
you would pursue? You would would you
spin a block? No. You good? just that's
just always going to be like my people
like like everything before a time and a
place and a reason for the season
sometime like and that just that's what
that was like it was just a reminder
like up or down you still that [ __ ]
like you I always had a pretty [ __ ] in
a jump shot like I said so Mandy just
came with like her tired of dealing with
celebrities that probably been you know
um
leaving her in limbo and then me being
on my down slide, [ __ ] with all these
nothing [ __ ] and then you finally
get like a chick with some status and
like you know some purpose and [ __ ] So
I'm thinking like maybe this the way I
need to go and stop [ __ ] with all
these rap boy stripper hoes and these
little gutter bugs and [ __ ] But that
[ __ ] don't be no different man. It's
like if it if the drinks don't mix it
ain't you know what I'm saying? Then
don't [ __ ] with it. You know what I
mean? Right.